Guide to the Independent Association of Publishers' Employees Records WAG.238
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
Independent Association of Publishers' Employees Records
1937-2003
1985-1995
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
Independent Association of Publishers' Employees
Communications Workers of America. Local 1096 (Princeton Junction, N.J.)
WAG.238
13 Linear Feet in 13 record cartons
The Independent Association of Publishers' Employees (IAPE) represents all categories of employees of Dow Jones and Company and the Wall Street Journal. The IAPE was founded in 1946 as the Dow Jones Employees Association of New York, and was renamed the Independent Association of Publishers' Employees in 1954. The IAPE maintained its independence through two failed attempts at affiliation with larger international unions, the Graphic Communications International Union in 1987, and the Communications Workers of America (CWA) in 1990. The membership finally approved affiliation to the CWA's Printing, Publishing and Media Workers Sector (PPMWS) in 1996, and the Association was chartered as Local 1096 of the CWA. The collection contains minutes, correspondence, bargaining files, administrative files, publicity material, background files on issues of concern to the union, photographs, and buttons.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Donated by the Communications Workers of America, Local 1096 (Independent Association of Publishers' Employees), in 2004. The accession numbers associated with this gift are 2004.013, 2004.016, and NPA.2006.029.
Historical/Biographical Note
The Independent Association of Publishers' Employees (IAPE) represents all categories of employees of Dow Jones & Company and the Wall Street Journal, including journalists, editors, printing plant workers, clerical and technical staff and sales staff. Workers in Information Technology are now the single largest group represented by the union. The IAPE was founded in 1946 as the Dow Jones Employees Association of New York. The union's name was intentionally broad to indicate that the union would represent not only Dow Jones' reporters and writers but all of the company's employees. The organization was renamed the Independent Association of Publishers' Employees in 1954 when it expanded to include the employees of The Wall Street Journal; the intent was also to indicate the future possibility of expanding the union's membership further. The local now includes workers at several Dow Jones-owned companies.
In 1977, when preparing for a union election in which he was challenging the incumbent president, Eric Frankland, a former IAPE vice-president, was denied permission to copy the names and addresses of IAPE members from union records. He filed suit against the union, but lost the case, which was then appealed to the New York Supreme Court. The final result, documented in the collection, was that Frankland was allowed to view the membership list, but would not be able to take notes, or make copies of the roster.
The IAPE maintained its independence through two failed attempts at affiliation with larger international unions, the Graphic Communications International Union in 1987, and the Communications Workers of America (CWA) in 1990. In 1996, under the leadership of president Ron Chen, the membership voted to approve affiliation to the CWA's Printing, Publishing and Media Workers Sector (PPMWS) becoming Local 1096 of the CWA. On January 1, 2000 the IAPE became part of the Newspaper Guild, which itself had affiliated with the CWA in 1998.
The IAPE has engaged in contentious negotiations with the management of Dow Jones and the Wall Street Journal over issues of job classification, pay rates, and workers' benefits. The union also became involved in the controversy over the Dow Jones Board of Directors' choice of Peter Kann as CEO. The IAPE was outspoken in protests over compensation agreements with Kann and his wife, Wall Street Journal publisher Karen Elliot House.
Scope and Content Note
The collection contains the records of the Independent Association of Publishers' Employees (IAPE) dating from 1937-2003 including Board of Directors minutes, bylaws, correspondence, bargaining files, administrative files, publicity material, background files on issues of concern to the union, photographs, and buttons.
Conditions Governing Access
Materials are open without restrictions.
Arrangement
The records are arranged in three series. The contents of each series are arranged alphabetically, and the contents of Series III: Photographs and Buttons are arranged alphabetically and chronologically. The series arrangement is as follows:
Series I: Bylaws, Constitutions and Minutes, 1937-1998
Series II: Subject Files, 1955-2003
Series III: Photographs and Buttons, circa 1986-2000
Custodial History
The archived website was migrated from the California Digital Library's Web Archiving Service to the Internet Archive's Archive-It Service in November 2015. The link to California Digital Library was removed in October 2017.
Publishers and publishing |z United States |x History.; Labor unions -- Organizing -- United States.; Affirmative Action programs.; Labor unions -- Officials and employees.; Publishers and publishing -- United States.; Labor unions |x Publishing |z United States.; Legal documents.; Collective labor agreements |x Publishing.; Company unions |x Publishing.; Photographs.; Buttons (information artifacts).; Arbitration, Industrial.; Labor unions -- Political activity -- United States.; Labor unions -- Contract administration.; Discrimination in employment.; Reports.; Minutes (administrative records); Financial records; Correspondence.; Labor unions -- Elections -- United States.; Fliers (printed matter); Clippings (information artifacts); Newspaper Guild of New York; Wall Street Journal (Firm); Dow Jones & Co; Communications Workers of America; Independent Association of Publishers' Employees; Communications Workers of America. Local 1096 (Princeton Junction, N.J.); Davis, Evelyn Y.; Chen, Ron.; Kann, Peter.; Communications Workers of America. Local 1096 (Princeton Junction, N.J.)
- Series I: Bylaws, Constitutions and Minutes, 1937-1998
  Scope and Content Note
  Series contains the bylaws of the union, copies of the incorporation documents for both the Dow Jones Employees Association and the Independent Association of Publishers' Employees, and minutes of the union's Board of Directors meetings.
  - Board of Directors Meeting, Jun 16, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Board of Directors Meeting, Dec 8, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Board of Directors Meeting, Apr 20, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Board of Directors Meeting, Apr 12, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Board of Directors Meeting, Jun 14, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Board of Directors Meeting, Sep 13, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Board of Directors Meeting, Jun 20, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Board of Directors Meeting, Oct 17, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Board of Directors Meeting, Jun 4, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Board of Directors Meeting, Oct 22, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Board of Directors Meeting, Apr 15, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Board of Directors Meeting, Sep 16, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Board of Directors-IAPE, 1990-1994 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Bylaws, 1975-1989 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Bylaws, 1995-1998 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Bylaws: Dow Jones, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Bylaws (from other Unions), 1997 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Dow Jones Employees Association and IAPE Incorporation Documents, 1946-1988 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Dow Jones Employees Association Minutes, 1937-1949 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Dow Jones Employees Association Treasurers Report, 1949-1952 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Series II: Subject Files, 1955-2003
  Series consists of records concerning affiliation, affirmative action, bargaining, job classification, contract proposals, court cases, Dow Jones policies, election of union officers, health care, legal and financial matters, publicity and organizing.
  - 401K Summary, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Accounts, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Accretion, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Accretion: Capital Markets Report, 1990-1992 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Accretion Cases, 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Accretion: International Brotherhood of Electric Workers(IBEW), 1992 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Accretion: Telerate, 1990-1992 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Accretion: Telerate Canada, 1992-1997 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Advertising: Transportation Displays Incorporated, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Advertising Sales Incentives, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Advertising Policies, 1994-1998 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Affiliation, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Affiliation, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Affiliation, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Affiliation (I), 1990 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Affiliation (II), 1990 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Affiliation, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Affiliation, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Affiliation, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Affiliation Agreement, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Affiliation Agreement (Original) and Application for Local Charter, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Affiliation Campaign Material, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Affiliation Correspondence, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Affiliation Correspondence, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Affiliation Financial Data, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Affiliation Memos, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Affiliation: Newspaper Guild, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Affiliation: Preparing for Future Efforts, 1985-1989 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Affiliation Publicity, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Affiliation Publicity, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Affiliation Vote, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Affirmative Action (I), 1986-1998 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Affirmative Action (II), 1986-1998 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Affirmative Action, 1995-2000 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Agency Fee Objectors (I), 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Agency Fee Objectors (II), 1998-1999 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Agency Shop, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Agreements, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Alternative Work Schedules, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Anti-Discrimination, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Arbitration Award, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Austerity, 1984-1990 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Ballot/Questionnaire: Completed Sample, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Bargaining, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Bargaining (I), 1993 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Bargaining (II), 1993 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Bargaining, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Bargaining, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Bargaining, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Bargaining and Mobilization Documents, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Bargaining Bulletins, 1993-1996 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Bargaining: Classification, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Bargaining: London and Tokyo, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Bargaining Notes, Sep 1995-Dec 1995 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Bargaining Notes, Jan 1996-May 1996 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Bargaining Notes, Jun 1996-Aug 1996 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Bargaining Notes, Sep 1996-Oct 1996 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Bargaining Notes, Nov 1996-Jan 1997 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Bargaining Notes, Feb 1997-Apr 1997 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Bargaining Notes: Chen, Dec 1995-Feb 1996 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Bargaining Notes: Chen, Mar 1996-May 1996 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Bargaining Proposals, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Bargaining Proposals, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Bargaining Proposals, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Bargaining: Publicity Campaign, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Bargaining: Questionnaire, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Bargaining Reference Material, 1955-1966 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Bargaining Reference Material, 1967-1969 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Bargaining: Sample Language, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Barron's, 1989-1993 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Bowling Green, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Bulletin Boards, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Buyouts, 1990-1992 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Calculated Pay Scales, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Canadian Issues, 1991-1993 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Canadian Issues, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Canadian Profit Sharing, 1984-1985 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Canadian Reporters, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Child Care, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Child Care: American Express Kidscheque Program, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Classification, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Classification, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Classification, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Classification Documents, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Classification Meeting, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Classification Proposals, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Classification Titles, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Collective Bargaining Agreement, 1990-1993 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Commission Incentive Plan, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Company Cars, 1992-1993 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Compensatory Increase, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Consent to Prosecute, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Conflict of Interest, 1992-1998 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Contract, 1968-1969 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Contract, 1990-1993 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Contract, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Contract: BGEA, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Contract Classifications, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Contract Documents, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Contract Language, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Contract Negotiations, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Contract Proposals, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Contract Proposals, 1996-1999 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Contract Provisions, 1993-1996 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Cornell University Labor Studies, 1992-1993 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, May 4, 1998-Feb 4, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, Feb 7, 1999-Nov 4, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, Nov 15, 1999-Jan 7, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, Jan 13, 2000-Aug 17, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence: Post-award, 2001-2002 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Cost of Living Allowance (COLA) Increase, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Council of Dow Jones Unions, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Court Case: Dismissal-Albury, Eric, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Court Case: Dismissal-McHale, Deborah, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Court Case: Membership List-Frankland, Eric NY State Supreme Court (I), 1977-1982 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Court Case: Membership List-Frankland, Eric NY State Supreme Court (II), 1977-1982 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Court Case: Membership List-Frankland, Eric NY State Supreme Court (III), 1977-1982 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Court Case: Union Policy-American Federation of Television and Radio Artists (AFTRA), 1981 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Current Annual Salary, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Customer Service Policy: Call Monitoring, 1997-1998 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Davis, Evelyn Y., 1992-1994 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Delinquent Membership Dues, 2001 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Dental Usage Data, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Department List, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Department of Labor: Local Union Ruling, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Department Roster, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Directors Guide, 1990-1991 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Disability, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Discrimination, 1991-1993 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Disincorporation, 1991-1997 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Domestic Partner Benefits, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Dow Jones: Agreements, 1969-1997 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Dow Jones: Annual Reports, 1969-1990 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Dow Jones: Board Meetings, 1994-1998 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Dow Jones: Board of Directors, 1995-1998 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Dow Jones: Bulletin, 1986-1990 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Dow Jones: Bulletin, 1991-1999 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Dow Jones: Code of Conduct, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Dow Jones: Corporate Structure, 1993-1998 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Dow Jones Employees Association, 1937-1944 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Dow Jones Employees Association: Contracts, 1945-1954 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Dow Jones: Financial Information, 1989-1993 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Dow Jones: Gay Issues, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Dow Jones: History, 1970-1981 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Dow Jones: Press Coverage, 2000-2003 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Dow Jones: Proposal for New Contract, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Dow Jones: Safety-Video Display Terminals (VDT's), 1991 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Dow Jones: Smoking Policy, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Dress Code, 1995-1998 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Dues Campaign, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Dues Increase Campaign, 1977-1993 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Dues Increase Campaign, 1999-2000 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Dues Reports, 2000-2001 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Dues Vote, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Dues Withdrawls, 1991-1994 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Earnings: First Quarter, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Earth Station Technologies and Operators Unit-South Brunswick, NJ, 1997-1998 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Eavesdropping, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Education Benefits, 1990-1991 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Election, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Election, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Election, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Election (I), 1991 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Election (II), 1991 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Election, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Election, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Election, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Election, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Election: Bylaws Vote, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Employee Assistance Program, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Employee Trip Reduction (ETR): New Jersey Transportation Plan, 1993-1994 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Executive Committee, 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Fact Sheet, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Family and Work Institute Publications, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Family Benefits, 1992-1993 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Family Issues, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Finance Committee, 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Financial Editor, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Financial News Network (FNN), 1991 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Financial Reports, 1980-1981 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Financial Reports, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Financial Reports, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Financial Reports, 1984-1985 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Financial Reports, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Financial Reports, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Financial Reports, 1990-1991 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Financial Reports, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Financial Reports, 1994-1996 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Fitness Program, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Fountain Housing Participants, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Full-time IAPE Employees, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Gay and Lesbian Issues, 1991-1992 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Grievance Committee: Minorities and Women, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Grievance Newsletter, Jul 1996 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Hand-billing at Princeton Junction, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Hay Group, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Health, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Health Benefits Surveys, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Health Care, 1991-1992 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Health Care, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Health Care: Dependent Care, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - Health Management Organization (HMO), 1992 (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - Health Plan, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - Health Plan Analyses, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - Health Plan Proposal, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - Health Policy, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - Hire Summary, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - Holidays, 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 49)
  - Human Rights Commission Case: Lenz, Mildred (I), 1988-1989 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Human Rights Commission Case: Lenz, Mildred (II), 1988-1989 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Human Rights Commission Case: Lenz, Mildred (III), 1988-1989 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Incentive Committee, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Incentive Committee Notes, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Incentive Committee Proposals, 1992-1993 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - IAPE Locations, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Indoor Air Quality, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Internal Issues, undated (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Job Descriptions, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Job Postings, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Journey Travel Quest International, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Kann, Peter, 1991-1998 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Key Bargaining Documents, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Language of Agreement on IAPE Proposal VII, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Labor Department, 1976-1982 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Las Colinas, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Layoffs, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Layoffs, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Layoffs: Marsh, Barbara, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Layoffs: Naperville, 1987-1991 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Legal Council, 1981-1995 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Legal Reports, 1974-1978 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Legal Reports, 1981-1988 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Legal Reports, 1991-1995 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Legal Reports, 1996-1997 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Legal Reports, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Markets, 1992-1998 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Martin, Ken, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Maryland: Overturn of Right to Work Law, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Media Stories on Dow Jones, Apr 1997-Sep 1997 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Media Stories on Dow Jones, Oct 1997-Dec 1997 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Media Stories on Dow Jones, 1998-2000 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Media Stories on IAPE, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Media Stories on Wall Street Journal Interactive (WSJI) and Dow Jones Interactive (DJI), 1996-1997 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Medical Plan, 1992-1993 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Membership Surveys, 1991-1992 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Member Statistics, 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Minorities Survey, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Minority Data, 1984-1991 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Minority Issues, 1972-1986 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Minority Issues (I), 1987-1999 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Minority Issues (II), 1987-1999 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Mobilization, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Moran Letter, Oct 23, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - National Committee on Pay Equity, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - National Labor Relations Board (NLRB) Case: Allison, Paul, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - NLRB Case: Canadian Profit Sharing, 1984-1987 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Negotiation Postings, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Negotiations Plan, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - News Clippings: Chicago Tribune, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - News Clippings: Contracts and Board of Directors, 1962-1995 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - News Clippings: Dow Jones CEO Choice, 1993-1997 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - News Clippings: Dow Jones Markets, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - News Clippings: Employee Benefits Cuts, 1998-2000 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - News Clippings: Information Industry, 1987-1998 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - News Clippings: The Journalist and Financial Reporting (TJFR), 1987-1990 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - News Clippings: NABET-CWA, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - News Clippings: Outside Press on Dow Jones (I), 1987-1999 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - News Clippings: Outside Press on Dow Jones (II), 1987-1999 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - News Clippings: Village Voice, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - News Clippings: Wall Street Journal (about WSJ), 1978-1990 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - News Department: New Employee Bargaining, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Newsletter, 1990-1993 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Newsletter, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Newsletter: Computer Issues, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Newsletter: Grievances, 1985-1996 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - The Newspaper Guild (TNG): Press Coverage, 1979-1997 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - TNG Update, Oct 1995 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - News Service Sales, 1993-1994 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Officer Pay, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Office Space, 1988-1991 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Open Shop Statement, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Operations Analyst, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Organizing: Calgary, Alberta Canada, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Organizing: Chicago, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Organizing: Fullerton, CA, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Organizing: Indianapolis, IN, 1975-1976 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Organizing: Offices Recognized by Dow Jones, 1968-1972 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Organizing: Ottaway, NY, 1971-1974 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Overheads, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Overseas Allowances, 1991-1992 (Box 10, Folder 25)